{
    "id": "a1000d621a224c79a254cf0ab4340052",
    "title": "Since, For, From, In",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He has been away …………………… six years.",
            "description": "Use for with perfect tenses to show duration.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "824318ea19a84b19b21c9f21e4259095"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has been learning classical music ………………………… five years.",
            "description": "Use for with perfect tenses to show duration.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3715aaf364fe45779157db8ed3c877ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was here ……………………… two months.",
            "description": "Use for to show duration.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "be04b7fb8003435e9af006dcbd84b5cd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t met her ………………………. I left college.",
            "description": "Use since with perfect tenses to indicate the starting point. ",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "464435d44d2c409f9675dd6d6fb882d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are going to Malaysia ……………………….. the summer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b00d6117c5f2464ba5f1bbb02ca989ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have been good friends ……………………….. our school days.",
            "description": "Use since with perfect tenses to indicate the starting point. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "30163308aaca4ef491adecd00b3cf1d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long have you been here …………………………?",
            "description": "Use for to indicate duration. ",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9912dbf07ed147d0bd343a13cadd5936"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. when have you been here?",
            "description": "Use since with perfect tenses to indicate the starting point. ",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "For",
                "From"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "64501bba7f214cf0b37e7364f541ed63"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was the best dinner I had …………………….. years.",
            "description": "Either in or for is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0bfdea6a2671428aa1fccb508d0e6b3a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be here …………………………. 3 o’clock onwards.",
            "description": "From is used with simple tenses. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "22ff84a061154a628456d3932d58f780"
        },
        {
            "question": "The shop is open ……………………….. six in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3e96ef259c1249babf563f4ba2cb23e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been waiting ………………………. morning.",
            "description": "Use since to indicate the starting point. ",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fa41c45b5caf4ce2887a050f265cd81a"
        }
    ]
}